<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfScene xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Scene>
    <Title>A Humbling Vista</Title>
    <Description>Before you lies a ledge just before a beautiful vista... and Derik is picking his nose again.</Description>
    <DefaultDialog>Holy cow! Come look at this drop! *Hiccup* Should I jump? I feel like I could probably fly if I jumped off here. What do you think?</DefaultDialog>
    <EndDialog>Jeeze you always have to ruin all the fun... I guess we can take the stairs. Only this once though. Next time I am totally jumping. </EndDialog>
    <Decisions>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Push Derik off the ledge</Action>
        <Response>Woah woah not so faaaaaaaaaaaaaaaast! I can fly! *Splat*</Response>
		<HeroState>Bloody Mess</HeroState>
	  </Decision>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Give Derik an aggrivated stare</Action>
        <Response>The silent treatment huh? Well I am going to stay positive here and guess at what you are thinking: "Wow, Derik is such a beautiful man, I bet he could totally fly off this ledge." That's it right? See you down there! *Splat*</Response>
		<HeroState>Bloody Mess</HeroState>
	  </Decision>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Punch Derik square in the nose</Action>
        <Response>*Whack* Ouch! That freaking hurt! What is wrong with you? Are you jealous of my incredibly beatiful face to the point of sabotaging my wonderful nose? Some people...</Response>
		<HeroState>Alive</HeroState>
      </Decision>
	  <Decision>
        <Action>Explain the effects of gravity to Derik</Action>
        <Response>See, this is why nobody likes you. You have to go full scholar on me when I am just trying to have a little fun. Besides, what's the worst that can happen? *SQUAAACK* What the hell is that? A giant parrot? AHHH NO! DON'T TAKE ME AWAY! HELP!</Response>
		<HeroState>Bird Food</HeroState>
      </Decision>
    </Decisions>
  </Scene>
  <Scene>
    <Title>An Old Cottage</Title>
    <Description>A structurally unsound cottage just barely stands in front of you.</Description>
    <DefaultDialog>Yes! Finally I can get some well-deserved rest! C'mon, lets go take a peek. Maybe there are some lonely maidens in there!</DefaultDialog>
    <EndDialog> Maybe we should just keep moving... You would probably scare off all the pretty maidens anyway, then I would be stuck with all the ugly ones like that one time in hero camp.</EndDialog>
    <Decisions>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Facepalm in annoyance</Action>
        <Response>Hey, there is a sign here... It says "Trespassers without a hand on their face will be shot with a large cannon." I wonder who put this *KABOOM!!!*</Response>
		<HeroState>Many Pieces</HeroState>
	  </Decision>
	  <Decision>
        <Action>Ignore Derik and keep walking</Action>
        <Response>Fine, be that way. I guess I will get all the ladies to myself. *Yells* Oh ladies! Come and get me! *ROAAAAR* What the heck is that? A freaking grizzly bear!? NO! NOT AGAIN! AAAAAHHHH! *CRUNCH*</Response>
		<HeroState>Bear Dinner</HeroState>
      </Decision>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Encourage Derik to explore the cottage</Action>
        <Response>What is this? There must be something terribly wrong with this cottage if you are actually agreeing with me here...</Response>
		<HeroState>Alive</HeroState>
	  </Decision>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Explain the lack of structural integrity to Derik</Action>
        <Response>Wow, you are literally the biggest negative-nancy I have ever met. If I lived life by your rules, I would never have touched totally awesome witch booty! That's it, I am going in. *CRRRASH*</Response>
		<HeroState>Squished</HeroState>
      </Decision>
    </Decisions>
  </Scene>
  <Scene>
    <Title>An Ice Cavern</Title>
    <Description>You are standing inside a beautiful cavern made of ice.</Description>
    <DefaultDialog>S-S-S-O-O-O C-C-O-L-D-D! I don't want to do this anymore! I don't even care about some stupid plague! Isn't that just the stuff you get on your teeth if you haven't brushed in a while? I'm going home! See ya!</DefaultDialog>
    <EndDialog>I hate you...</EndDialog>
    <Decisions>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Threaten Derik with a sharp icicle</Action>
        <Response>What is the meaning of this? I'm not scared of your flimsy water-weapon! See this? This is me walking away *Slips and falls on icicle*</Response>
		<HeroState>Impaled</HeroState>
	  </Decision>
	  <Decision>
        <Action>Put ice chunks down Derik's armor</Action>
        <Response>*Girly Scream* COLD! OH HOLY COW! AAAAHHHH! GET IT OUT! I'LL KEEP GOING I PROMISE!</Response>
		<HeroState>Alive</HeroState>
      </Decision>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Talk some sense into Derik</Action>
        <Response>I legitimately do not care right now. I am freezing my nips off in here, you try wearing plate armor in an ice-box! *RRRAAAAWWWWWRRR* What was that? On no... A YETI!? A FREAKING YETI!? NO! GET AWAY! *CHOMP*</Response>
		<HeroState>Yeti Snack</HeroState>
	  </Decision>
      <Decision>
        <Action>Give up all hope</Action>
        <Response>How am I supposed to maintain my handsome smile with your constant moping around? Just because I am going back home doesn't mean I can't still be beautiful. Hello? Where did you go? Oh no! AM I LOST!? HELP! MY LOOKS ALONE CAN'T KEEP ME WARM IN HERE!</Response>
		<HeroState>Forever Lost</HeroState>
      </Decision>
    </Decisions>
  </Scene>
</ArrayOfScene>